{
    "subject": "Carol_Rosin",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jon_Cypher",
    "human_readable": "Carol Rosin is married to Jon Cypher.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.982788622379303,
            "question": "Is Jon Cypher's spouse named Carol Rosin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9068772196769714,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Carol Rosin and Jon Cypher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9009127616882324,
            "question": "Name the person married to Jon Cypher."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8910844326019287,
            "question": "To whom is Carol Rosin married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8826372027397156,
            "question": "Who is married to Jon Cypher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8276212215423584,
            "question": "Who are Jon Cypher and Carol Rosin related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6518594026565552,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Jon Cypher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6483011245727539,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Cypher's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6148373484611511,
            "question": "Is Carol Rosin in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4199027121067047,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Cypher's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carol Rosin is married to Jon Cypher.",
            "html": "yago_5853_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Carol Rosin in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_5853_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jon Cypher's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_5853_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Jon Cypher?",
            "html": "yago_5853_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5853_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Carol Rosin was born on March 29, 1944 in Wilmington, Delaware, USA. She is married to Jon Cypher.\" and \"He married Carol Rosin after divorcing his first wife, Ruth Wagner, in 1975.\" This confirms the statement \"Carol Rosin is married to Jon Cypher.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}